<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Newsroom</title><link>https://lexlogic.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Newsroom</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2019, Weru and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lexlogic.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring the JWT Attacks Landscape</title><link>https://lexlogic.github.io/post/2022-10-03-research-jwt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lexlogic.github.io/post/2022-10-03-research-jwt/</guid><description>What is JWT ? JWT, or JSON Web Token, is an open standard (RFC 7519) used to exchange security information between a client and a server. Due to its popularity, JWT attacks are one of of the most exploited vulnerability by attackers. Each JWT contains base64 encoded JSON objects. A cryptographic algorithm is used to sign JWT tokens to ensure the token&amp;rsquo;s integrity and protect against JWT attacks.
JWT structure JSON web tokens consist of three parts separated by dots (.</description></item><item><title>VAmPI the vulnerable API for security testing</title><link>https://lexlogic.github.io/post/2022-10-02-training-api/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lexlogic.github.io/post/2022-10-02-training-api/</guid><description>Well it was one of this times where in an attempt to &amp;ldquo;fix a light bulb&amp;rdquo; a series of events lead you to do something else first. For those who do not know what I am talking about, go ahead and spend 40 seconds to watch this video.
I was trying to assess how well certain tools perform on finding vulnerabilities in APIs. In order to do that, I required a vulnerable API that could cover vulnerabilities included in the OWASP top 10 for APIs and that it would be consistent in its responses across different endpoints.</description></item></channel></rss>